

OLHA SHULHA QA Engineer

O Ukraine, Odessa

+38(067)958-49-64

olgashulga13@gmail.com @olhashulha13

in olh<u>a-shulha</u>

olhashulha



I am looking for a position as a "QA Engineer" with 15+ years of communication skills, attention to detail, and ready to work on challenging tasks.

Experience in bug tracking systems and test management tools, such as Jira, Mantis, and TestLink. Understanding of software development methodologies, knowledge of client-server architecture. English - Intermediate.



TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- Bug Tracking system and test management tool: Jira, Mantis, TestLink
- Linux Terminal (pwd, cd, ls, mkdir, cd, find, grep, touch, nano, vim, cp, cat, sending requests, etc.) Link on github.com
- GitHub/GitBash (add, commit, push, pull, checkout, branch) merge, Link on github.com
- Postman (Sending requests, creating environments, running collections) Link on github.com
- **HTML5/CSS3 (CV_Link and Landing page on github.com)**
- Android SDK (building apk and running an emulator) Link on github.com
- **SQL** <u>Link on github.com</u>
- Chrome DevTools Link on github.com
- **Documentation** (Checklists, bug-reports, test-cases).
- **Theory of testing** (types, levels, and methods of testing. SDLC, STLC, attributes of bug-report, test-case, checklist, client-server architecture).

LANGUAGE SKILLS:

- English/Intermediate
- German/Elementary
- Hebrew/Pre-Intermediate



SOFT SKILLS:

- Attentive to details
- Responsible

- Constant learner
- Time-management



EDUCATION & TRAINING:

January 2022 | The Fundamentals of Software Testing in QATestLab Training Center. May - August 2021 | Author courses of software testing by Vadim Ksendzov. September 2002 - June 2003 | Odessa State Academy of Refrigeration, Master Degree, Cryogenic engineering and technology.



EXPERIENCE:

April 2005 - present | Entrepreneur Shulha, dealer of the "ABC-Keramik", Germany. Executable functions:

- Market analysis.
- o Working with the German manufacturer, banking and customs operation.
- Technical customer support, advertising, and development of the website.

October 2003 - April 2005 | Agrotech LLC, Manager.